With Amazon Global Selling, you can expand your business and reach customers across the globe by
listing your products in Amazon stores worldwide.
Use the "sell globally" experience to discover your top countries and Amazon stores for expansion.
Determine your costs of selling in these new stores and receive expert guidance and resources to
launch successfully.
Access "sell globally" by navigating to the main seller central menu, hovering over the inventory
tab and clicking on "sell globally".
The new stores to launch section uses two different views to help you explore your potential in
additional stores.
Region view compares your opportunity across different regions, including potential sales, any incentives
Amazon provides to support your launch,
and an estimate of the year one investment you would make to expand to your highest potential store.
Store view shows similar data, plus recommended ASINs in a table view.
This view is especially useful if you have multiple stores to consider expanding into.
The next section, "Global Sales in Active Stores" lets you view a summary of your sales performance
in your current stores,
plus an estimate of your sales opportunity when available.
Stores will only appear in the "Global Sales in Active Stores" section if you already have an account
in that store.
If you have an account in another store that is not showing up in "Global Sales in Active Stores",
you may need to link it to your other accounts.
Scroll down to "Amazon Stores Worldwide" and click "Link Account" next to that store.
And when you're ready to expand to a new store listed in the "Amazon Stores Worldwide" table, simply
click "Register" next to the new store.
You can access powerful data about your expansion opportunities on the expansion research page,
which you can get to from the new stores to launch section by clicking on "View Details in Region
View" or "Details in Store View".
You can also get to the expansion research page from the "Global Sales in Active Stores" section
by clicking on a sales opportunity amount if available.
When you're on the expansion research page, select a region from the drop-down and then select a
specific store to see relevant data.
You'll see a summary of the opportunity in that store, including your estimated first-year sales
and the cost to launch in that store based on the top ASINs which are displayed as well.
Under the "Summary", the "Sales Insights" tab shows category trends and predicted demand for your
catalog in the target store.
Sales projection by category is the first chart shown and you can filter the data by your current
catalog's categories or brands and can compare between gross merchandise sales or GMS and number
of units.
Beneath this chart, you will see six graphs, which you can filter by category and time frame.
These charts show category sales trend, top ASINs sales, sales across price bands, return ratio,
advertising cost of sales and Amazon fees comparison.
For some target stores, you will also see the "Cost Analysis" tab, which shows an estimate of the
variable and one-time costs of your first year, assuming you launch your top 10 recommended ASINs
in the target store.
These costs are estimates only and final costs depend on various factors.
The estimated sales, incentive to launch if applicable, variable costs and one-time costs are outlined
in the "Cost Breakdown" table on the left.
Click on the drop-down arrow for each estimate to see more details.
On the right, Amazon will provide estimated shipping costs and estimates for additional ASIN specific
costs if these estimates are applicable and available.
Use the links in this section to explore additional programs and find trusted service providers
to support your expansion journey.
When you're ready to expand to the target store, simply click "Sign Up" at the top of the Expansion
Research page to be taken to the Account Registration page for that store.